indialinks.com 2010-12-31

# Domain Names, Domain Registration, Web Hosting, Email Hosting, SSL Certificates

Privacy Statement

IndiaLinks respects the privacy and security of its customers and users of its website.

We have prepared this Privacy Policy to enable you to understand which personal identifying information of yours is collected, how and when we might use your information, how we protect your information, who has access to your information, and how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

###### Information We Collect

IndiaLinks collects certain information from and about its users three ways: (i) from our web server logs, (ii) with cookies and (iii) directly from the user. _Web server logs_ : 

When you visit our website, IndiaLinks may collect information to administer the site and analyze its usage. IndiaLinks may collect information such as: 

  * your Internet protocol address;
  * the type of browser or computer you use; 
  * the number of links you click within our website; 
  * the state or country from which you accessed our website; 
  * the date and time of your visit; 
  * the name of your Internet service provider; 
  * the Web page from which you linked to our website; and 
  * the pages you viewed on our website 

_Cookies_ :

IndiaLinks' website use cookies (i.e., small bits of text that our servers place into a file on your computer's hard drive). We use cookies to save your preferences and login information, and provide personalized functionality. You can reject cookies by changing your browser settings, but be aware that this will disable some of the functionality on IndiaLinks' website. 

_Personal information users give us_ :

On some pages of our website, users can register to purchase products or services, receive personalized content and participate in surveys or forums. When you register, IndiaLinks may ask you for some personal information. 

If you're purchasing products or services, we may also request financial information such as credit card or bank account information. Any financial information we collect is used only to bill you for the products and services you purchased. If you purchase by credit card, this information may be forwarded to your credit card provider. For other types of registrations, we will ask for your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number. We may then contact you with information about IndiaLinks products and services. As a security measure and to ensure that our website and computer network remain available to all customers, IndiaLinks may use software programs to monitor network traffic or to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. These software programs may also collect information regarding your use of our website and computer network. 

You may also be asked to disclose personal information to us so that we can provide technical support assistance and information to you. For example, we may collect personal information from you (such as an e-mail address, system information and problem descriptions) in order to provide online technical support and troubleshooting. If you choose to correspond with us through electronic communication (e.g. email, online chat or instant messaging), we may retain a copy of the electronic communication together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone. 

Finally, some pages of the IndiaLinks' website may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, news groups or instant messaging available to you. Please remember that any information disclosed in these areas is public. You should exercise caution when disclosing personal information in these areas. Don't disclose information in these public forums that might be considered confidential - such as financial information, social security numbers, passwords or email addresses. Users should be aware that when they voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information on the bulletin boards or in the chat areas, that information and any substantive information disclosed in the communication can be collected and used by third parties. This could result in unsolicited messages from others who post on such sites and are beyond the control of IndiaLinks. 

###### How We Use Your Information

IndiaLinks uses the information we collect to process and deliver products & services you have ordered, notify you about your account and to notify you about changes to the terms and conditions governing your use of our website, products and services. We may also use the information we collect to seek your feedback, notify you about other products and services we think you will find valuable and about special offers. You may notify us of your desire not to receive notifications relating to new products and services and special offers by 'opting-out' as provided for below. 

IndiaLinks may also provide aggregate information about our customers, this website's traffic patterns and related website usage information to our affiliates and reputable third parties, but this information will not include personally identifying data. We take measures to select product or service providers that are responsible and afford similar privacy protections to their customers. However, we do not make any representations about the practices and policies of these companies. 

If you don't want to receive promotional materials from IndiaLinks or our marketing partners, you may opt out at any time by contacting us at sales@indialinks.com. 

###### How We Protect Your Information

IndiaLinks makes every effort to follow industry standard security measures to prevent the loss, misuse, alteration or unauthorized disclosure of information under our control. 

When we ask customers or users to provide financial information (such as a credit card number) that data is protected using Secure Sockets Layer ('SSL') technology. However, please note that electronic communication (e.g. email, online chat or instant messaging) that you may send to us may not be secure unless we advise you in advance that security measures will be in place prior to your transmitting the information. For that reason, we ask that you do not send confidential information such as financial information, social security numbers or passwords to us through unsecured electronic communication. 

###### Access to Your Information

IndiaLinks will share or disclosure your personal data in following ways :

  * as required by law, in a matter of public safety or policy, or as compelled by a court of law;
  * with other affiliates or partners of IndiaLinks (as described above);
  * with agents and contractors who use such information on behalf of IndiaLinks or in connection with administering or delivering products and services on behalf of IndiaLinks;
  * to enforce the terms and conditions of the products or services; 
  * to protect and defend IndiaLinks' or its Affiliates' rights, interests or property; 
  * as needed in connection with the transfer of business assets.

IndiaLinks restricts access to Personal Information to its employees, contractors and agents and provides such Personal Information only on a need to know basis in order to operate, develop or improve its services 

###### Links to Other Websites

IndiaLinks website contain links to sites maintained by other companies that are not affiliated IndiaLinks. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those sites, and we encourage you to use caution when visiting them. In particular, we recommend you view the privacy policy posted on each site. 

###### How to Correct Inaccuracies

If you've registered with our website, you can access and update your information online at MyIndiaLinks. Otherwise, you may contact us at sales@indialinks.com 

###### Privacy Policy Changes

IndiaLinks hereby reserves the right to amend, alter, modify, replace or suspend this Privacy Policy, from time to time, in its sole discretion. All such changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective when posted on IndiaLinks' website.  |   
---|---
